David M. Stowe Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Addendum - 2011, 1881-2001; Series XI
  - Personal Items and Memorabilia
    - Slides
      - List to accompany Angola slides, n.d. (Box 243, Folder 246)
      - Cassette and list to accompany Rhodesia slides (Box 243, Folder 247)
      - Slides of images from Africa, Australia, Latin America, Middle East, and Ecumenical/Board related events (Box 244, Folder 248)
- Addendum - material received from Andover Newton Theological School - 2017, Series XII
  - Papers related to Theological Education Fund, 1970-1977 (Box 245–248)
    The material includes working papers, minutes, and reports of annual meetings of the Theological Education Fund from the years when Stowe served as United Board for World Ministries (UCC)representative to the Fund. From 1958 to 1977 the Theological Education Fund focused on strengthening and renewing theological education in developing countries. In 1977 it was superseded by the Programme on Theological Education, a sub-unit of the World Council of Churches.
  - Directory of Theological School and related institutions in Africa, Asia, the Caribbean, Latin America & South Pacific - published by Theological Education Fund, 1974 (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - A Theological Book List - published by Theological Education Fund, 1968 (Box 248, Folder 5)
- Addendum - 2018, Series XIII
  - Correspondence